thomasville.com 2017-04-04

# Privacy Policy | Thomasville Furniture

Effective Date: January 2014

Heritage Home Group LLC (“HHG”, “we” or “us”) and our brands, which include but are not limited to Thomasville, Drexel Heritage, Broyhill, Henredon, Hickory Chair, La Barge, Lane, Lane Venture, Maitland-Smith and Pearson, value our customers and respect your privacy. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you what Personal Information we may collect from you, how we use such information, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to review and correct the information. This policy applies only to customers in the United States who have provided Personal Information to us through the Sites.

For purposes of this policy, “Personal Information” means any information by which you can be personally identified, and includes your name, your address, your telephone number, your e-mail address and the like or as otherwise defined by applicable law. Most of our websites do not require that you submit Personal Information to us. There may be times (such as when you purchase or order a product or register to participate in contests, etc.) when we ask you to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, shipping/billing address, telephone number, email address, credit card information, etc., and if you make a purchase, we may also maintain a record of your product purchases. In addition, our web servers may automatically recognize information regarding your domain name (or that of your access provider) and e-mail address, and we may use this data for trends and statistics, but individual users will remain anonymous, unless you voluntarily tell us who you are.

## California Residents

At this time, HHG reserves the right to disclose your personal information to any third-party for its marketing purposes. As such, under California Civil Code Sections 1798.80-1798.84, California residents have the right to obtain what information and to whom the information was provided by HHG in the immediately preceding calendar year.  
Therefore, upon written receipt of a written or email request for such information to the designated address below, HHG shall provide a list of any disclosures of the California resident’s personal information to any third party for their direct marketing purposes within thirty (30) days of the receipt of such request. The list shall include:

  1. A list of categories of personal information provided to any third party; and
  2. The names and addresses of all of third parties that received the California resident’s personal information for the third party’s direct marketing purposes within the preceding calendar year.

Such list may be in a standardized format and not specific to any individual.

## Utah Residents

We may choose to disclose nonpublic personal information about you, the consumer, to a third-party for compensation.

## Information We May Collect

IP Address  
We may log all connections to our web servers. Those log files will include your IP address. An IP address is NOT personally identifiable information, but general information about your location, connection to the Internet, and your Internet Service Provider. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Sites. Additionally, we will use your IP address to track your navigation of the Sites and any internal website searches. We reserve the right use your navigation history and information related to your use of the Sites in current and future marketing efforts to you and to others.

Cookies  
The Sites use "cookies," which are small data files that are stored on your computer when you visit a website. Cookies enable you to shop on our websites and may be used in a variety of ways to enhance or personalize your online browsing and shopping experience. 

For example, we may use cookies to enable you to use certain website features, remember the items in your shopping cart, store your preferences, recognize you when you return to our websites, track your orders, and monitor and maintain information about your use of our websites. 

You can set your browser not to accept cookies or to notify you when you are sent a cookie, giving you the opportunity to decide whether or not to accept it. If you do not accept cookies, however, you will not be able to access your account information or make purchases on our websites.

Clear Gifs  
We may also employ a software technology called clear gifs (also known as web beacons) that help us better manage content on our Sites by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users. Clear gifs and cookies are not tied to the user's personally identifiable information.

Personal Information Provided on a Contact or Registration Form or Through Your On-line Purchase  
Much of the information contained on the Sites is available without registering or supplying personal information. In the event you affirmatively act to register for an account on the Sites, request additional information via the Sites, or voluntarily supply information to HHG by registering on the Sites or submitting an information request form, you agree to the following terms regarding your contact and personal information in addition to the general terms of this Privacy Policy tied to use of the Sites. The Sites’ contact/information request and registration forms request that users provide contact and other personal information (such as their name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, phone,). The Sites may collect similar information to complete a purchase through the Sites and may additionally request credit card or other payment information.

## Usage of Your Personal Information

In general, we use the Personal Information you provide only for internal purposes, such as: • for the specific purpose for which it was volunteered (for example, to complete a product purchase, to enter a contest, to answer an e-mail, etc.); • to improve the content, appearance and utility of our websites; • to track our visitors’ use of our websites for internal market research; and • to notify our visitors of updates to the websites or of new products or services.

From time to time, we may contract with companies or persons to provide certain services including credit card processing, shipping, data management, promotional services, etc. We may provide these providers with the information needed for them to perform these services. From time to time we might also establish a business relationship with other persons or entities that we believe trustworthy. In such cases we might rent, exchange, share and/or cross–reference information, including contact information about you that will enable such persons or entities to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you. In addition, we may use third-party advertising companies to serve or track ads on our websites and other websites. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

In addition, we may operate sweepstakes, contests, raffles and similar promotions through our websites that may require online registration. We typically ask you for certain personally identifiable information when you enter and, if applicable, win a sweepstake, contest, raffle or similar promotion. We may share this personally identifiable information with third party sponsors of such sweepstakes, contests, raffles and promotions (irrespective of whether it is hosted by us), or otherwise in accordance with the rules applicable to such sweepstakes, contest, raffle or promotion. You should carefully review the rules of each sweepstake, contest, raffle and promotion in which you participate through our websites, as they may contain additional important information about our or a sponsor’s use of your personally identifiable information. Insofar as the terms and conditions of such rules concerning the treatment of your personally identifiable information conflict with this privacy statement, the terms and conditions of such rules shall control.

## Editing, Updating, Correcting And Deleting Information About You

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive direct marketing from us or from any third parties, or if you would like to opt out of our sharing your information with other marketers, please let us know. To edit or update your Personal Information or if you prefer not to receive information from us or any or all of our brands or any third parties, you can do so by contacting us by email or postal mail at the addresses below. Please be sure to include your email address, mailing address, full name, and specifically what information you do not want to receive.

Write to:   
Heritage Home Group LLC   
Attn: Corporate Communications   
1925 Eastchester Drive   
High Point, NC 27265

## Protecting Children

We take special care to protect the safety and privacy of children. We will never knowingly request personally identifiable information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. Our websites are general audience websites and are not targeted to or intended for use by children.

## Security

We take precautions to protect the security of your Personal Information that you share with us. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our websites, and you do so at your own risk.

## Links to Third Party Sites

Our websites may contain links to websites operated and maintained by third parties, over which we have no control. Privacy policies on such linked websites may be different from our privacy policy. You access such linked websites at your own risk. You should always read the privacy policy of linked websites before disclosing any Personal Information on such websites.

## Policy Changes

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this privacy policy at any time. You should check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes to this privacy policy will mean that you accept those changes.
